itsvit.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy | IT Svit ★ Managed DevOps Services Provider

IT Svit is committed to protecting the privacy of the visitors of IT Svit website, individuals who register to use our services, and business partners. The following privacy notices explain our privacy practices related to these activities and how IT Svit may collect, use, and/or share personal information.

[The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://www.eugdpr.org/), enforced May 25, 2018, imposes additional requirements upon companies to strengthen the security around and enhance the protection of personal data of EU residents. IT Svit has a dedicated, cross-functional team overseeing IT Svit GDPR readiness. We discuss IT Svit efforts and commitment to GDPR below.

The Cookie Policy described below addresses how we use cookies when you visit IT Svit. We want to be clear about how we collect and use data related to you via cookies.

This Privacy Policy applies to this Site. When visiting any Site, please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. By entering and using the Site you declare your agreement with this privacy statement.

By using this Site, you expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that your Personal Information gained in connection with your use of the Site, with respect to the Site, may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration) for operating and developing the Site, including transfers to IT Svit agents or representatives, who perform tasks related to the Site and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant databases.

## Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected

IT Svit  (hereinafter “IT Svit”) is committed to the protection of privacy of the Site visitors.

Please note that IT Svit may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to trusted third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.

## Personal Information

IT Svit collects Personal Information for the purposes of the provision, development, and personalization of the Site, services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics and customer care. Specifically, IT Svit collects personal information for the purposes of personal communication with you in order to respond to your questions, and fulfill your requests.

Such information may include, among other information, your name, address, email address and phone number. This data will be used in the events you have so consented, to contact you for direct marketing purposes via email or phone to conduct market research and to inform you of and get your feedback on upcoming products, services and/or promotions.

If you send us product orders, service requirements or if you send any material to the Site, we might have to contact you in order to gain additional information necessary for processing or fulfillment of your orders and/or requirements. Your Personal Information will not be revealed to any third parties without your prior consent unless required otherwise by legal regulations, or cases, when it is necessary for proceeding with your order, fulfilling your request, or providing interactive customer service, or IT Svit products and services improvement. At the same time, you are granting IT Svit the right to provide the information you submitted to IT Svit for above purposes to the partners cooperating with IT Svit.

## Personal Information Security

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or any other media or terminal, and no system of technology is completely safe, “tamper” or “hacker-proof”, IT Svit has endeavored to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your Personal Information. For example, when collecting or transferring sensitive data, e.g. banking card information, we use encrypting technology.

## The accuracy of Collected Data

IT Svit will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal information retained by IT Svit in connection with the operation of the Site.

## Visitors Identification through Cookies

Generally, you may use this Site for information purposes without giving personal information and informing IT Svit who you are. But, from time to time, IT Svit may place information on your computer to allow IT Svit to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as “cookies”. The cookies are commonly used on many websites. Cookies are stored on your hard disc in the computer, not on the IT Svit Site. IT Svit will use only the information we ourselves placed in cookies through the Site.

Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. By means of cookies, IT Svit is able to further develop and improve the Site. No personal information about you is gathered through the use of these types of cookies. In other words, cookies are identifying your computer, not you.

If you do not wish to receive cookies, or you want to be notified when a cookie is set, you can configure your browser, if the browser allows given settings. If you choose to decline cookies, please be aware that you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site, nor you will be able to download certain contents and/or to take part in certain transactions on the Site.

Besides, the Site may use different technology (Albacross), which enables IT Svit to collect certain technical information, for example, your IP address, type of operating system in your computer, Internet browser type and addresses of connected sites, in order to improve provided services.

IT Svit may use third party scripts on our sites to optimize the effectiveness of IT Svit’s ads appearing on other parties’ sites, such as the type and/or frequency of ads, promotions, or other marketing messages the customer views.

The information collected is not personally identifiable and is limited to the minimum information necessary to optimize effectiveness.

By using or accessing our Site, you agree to this Cookie Policy. This Policy may change from time to time and your continued use of our Site is deemed to be acceptance of such changes. Please check the Policy periodically for updates.

Available Cookie Opt-out – Google Analytics: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

## Minors

No information may be submitted to IT Svit via the Site by persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardians before submitting any information to IT Svit via the Site, with the exception if such activities are allowed by the applicable law of your country.

## Modification of the Privacy Policy

IT Svit reserves the right to change or modify at any time this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or deny access to the Site, or their content without prior notice.

## External Links

The Sites may contain links to third-party sites. Since IT Svit does not control nor is responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third-party sites. This Policy applies solely to personal data collected by our Sites or in the course of our business activities.

## Your Rights

Subject to applicable law, you may have rights available to you in respect of your personal data, including:

  * to obtain a copy of your personal data together with information about how and on what basis that personal data is processed
  * to rectify inaccurate personal data (including the right to have incomplete personal data completed)
  * to erase your personal data (in limited circumstances, such as where it is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed)
  * to restrict processing of your personal data under certain circumstances
  * to port your data in a machine-readable format to a third party (or to you) when we justify our processing on the basis of your consent or the performance of a contract with you
  * to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal data (where that processing is based on your consent)
  * to obtain, or see a copy of the appropriate safeguards under which your personal data is transferred to a third country or international organization.

In addition to the above rights, you have the right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to any processing of your personal data for which we have justified on the basis of a legitimate interest, including profiling (as opposed to your consent) or to perform a contract with you. You also have the right to object at any time to any processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes, including profiling for marketing purposes.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority for data protection.

In relation to all of these rights, please contact us at [info@itsvit.org](mailto:info@itsvit.org). Please note that we may request proof of identity, and we reserve the right to charge a fee where permitted by law, especially if your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive. We will endeavor to respond to your request within all applicable timeframes.

If you contact us regarding Customer Data for which we are a data processor, we will attempt to refer your request to the relevant Customer, and the data controller for your personal data.

## Service-Specific Terms

IT Svit may have separate terms for different services (for example the Terms of Usage), in which the service specific terms and conditions might be set forth (including data protection).
